{
    "subject": "resource/Laurence_Marks_(British_writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/Shine_on_Harvey_Moon",
    "human_readable": "Laurence Marks' notable work is 'Shine on Harvey Moon'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8359127640724182,
            "question": "Is 'Shine on Harvey Moon' a critically acclaimed work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8023289442062378,
            "question": "Which type of creative work is 'Shine on Harvey Moon'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7414868474006653,
            "question": "Name a notable work by Laurence Marks."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5710676312446594,
            "question": "What is the title of Laurence Marks' most famous work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5327058434486389,
            "question": "What genre does 'Shine on Harvey Moon' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4991813004016876,
            "question": "Has 'Shine on Harvey Moon' won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49586454033851624,
            "question": "Is 'Shine on Harvey Moon' a novel, a film, or a television series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4390886723995209,
            "question": "What is Laurence Marks known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35829654335975647,
            "question": "What other works has Laurence Marks created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34307804703712463,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Laurence Marks' career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laurence Marks' notable work is 'Shine on Harvey Moon'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8705_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other works has Laurence Marks created?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8705_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Laurence Marks known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8705_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Shine on Harvey Moon' a novel, a film, or a television series?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8705_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8705_69.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly mention that Laurence Marks and Maurice Gran wrote the television show \"Shine on Harvey Moon,\" which supports the statement that Laurence Marks' notable work is \"Shine on Harvey Moon.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}